医生 救援 医生
Doc,help,doc!
已经不出血了
It's not bleeding
那是因为血一接触空气就冻结了
That's because your blood's/freezing as it's hitting the air.
喔!
Ow!
这儿 用力压着
Here, apply pressure on it.
我想我的腿也冻住了
I think my leg is frozen.
那根本算不上什么大麻烦
That's the least of your problems.
桨叶割断了你的股动脉
The blade severed your femoral artery.
我这条腿是不是废了?
Am I gonna lose my leg?
冻伤不算严重 现在我要收拾你股动脉
Frost bite's not too bad but/I gotta fix your artery now.
会很疼的
This is gonna hurt.
你要把那弄进伤口里?
You're gonna put that in me?
这种温度下 胶水是修复动脉最好的办法
Glue's the best way to repair/your artery at this temperature.
看起来没问题了
It looks okay.
给 撕些下来 我得检查一下你的脚
Here,tear off some pieces.I/have to check your foot.
血流看来还好
Blood flow looks good.
你的腿应该没问题
Your leg should be okay.
我还以为我玩完了
I thought I was done.
我才不会让你出事
Yeah,like I'd let anything happen to you.
只有你能修好发电机
You're the only one who/can fix the generators.
一 二 三
One two three.
- 啊!/- Cate cate 你还好吧?
- Ah!/- Cate, cate, are you okay?
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
嘿
Hey.
我 我需要帮助
I I I need help.
我还能找谁?
Who am I supposed to get?
给你办公室真是多此一举
Why do I even give you an office?
新病例 精神科点名要你来治
New case.Psych department/asked for you personally.
病人是个疯子?
Patient's a crazy person?
你才是个疯子
You're a crazy person.
病人是个精神病医生
Patient's a psychiatrist.
昏迷佬的有线电视不太对劲
There's something wrong/with coma guy's cable.
他似乎对此没意见
He seems fine with it.
你的病人是这里的客座医生 但此刻
Your patient is an adjunct faculty/member here but currently
预算委员会决定对病房内的有线电视收费
the budget committee voted to charge/for cable in the patient rooms.
每况愈下
Slippery slope.
今天克扣色情电视/明天就轮到清洁绷带了
Today we withhold porn,tomorrow/it's clean bandages.
去跟皮肤科的Carlson说吧/他运作预算委员会
Talk to carlson in derm  he/runs the budget committee
你先看看这个
after you look at this.
你跟Carlson谈过之后 也许我会
After you talk to Carlson,maybe I'll
病人被困在南极
the patient is trapped/at the south pole.
能不能把她撤离回来?
Any possibility of evacuating her?
那就没乐趣了
That wouldn't be any fun.
而且接下来两个月里
And for the next two months,
强风使得飞机无法进出那里
winds make it impossible/to fly anything in or out.
可能是阑尾炎或胆结石
could be appendicitis  or a gallstone.
或者肾结石
Or a kidney stone.
那就没乐趣了
That wouldn't be any fun.
如果在那儿得阑尾炎
If it's appendicitis  down there,
她的阑尾破裂 她死掉 我们什么也做不了
her appendix ruptures,she/dies,there's nothing we can do.
如果是结石 她吃止痛药
If it's stones,she takes pain meds,
结石流出 我们什么也不用做了
the stone passes,there's/nothing we need to do.
可能是鸟粪石类的肾结石(感染引起)
Could be a struvite kidney stone.
大多数肾结石都是良性的钙质
Most kidney stones/are calcium and benign.
你为什么会怀疑鸟粪石?
Why would you suspect a struvite stone?
因为他说肾结石太无聊
'Cause he said kidney/stones were boring.
有这个可能
it's possible.
她在避孕
She's on birth control.
频繁的性生活引起尿道感染
Lots of sex could lead to/urinary tract infection,
引发因感染出现的鸟粪状结石
which could lead to an/infection-laced struvite kidney stone.
在南极过度钻孔
Excessive antarctic drilling.
对环境和女士都不好
Bad for the environment and the ladies.
如果是鸟粪石 得快点粉碎
If it's a struvite stone she/needs to break it up quickly
不然感染会造成肾衰竭
before the infection/shuts down her kidneys.
这就是有意思的地方了
This is where it gets fun.
这些是她现有的器材和药物
These are the supplies and/medications she has available.
这里没有能粉碎肾结石的
Nothing here that can/break up a kidney stone.
那儿还有其它的什么吗?
What else do they have down there?
- 我刚说过/- 我不是指医疗器材 其他东西
- I just said /- I don't mean medical stuff.other stuff
有些地质仪器能像粉碎结石一样破冰碎石
Some geological equipment breaks ice and/rock the same way we break kidney stones.
呃 探索频道
Uh,discovery channel.
我喜欢看他们爆破东西
I like watching them blow stuff up.
有谁不呢?
Who doesn't?
那提醒了我
That reminds me.
昏迷佬需要有线电视
coma guy needs cable.
是女子台球赛维系着他的生命
Women's billiard is the only/thing that's keeping him alive.
我相信Carlson定会被他的悲惨境遇感动
I'm sure Carlson will/be moved by his plight.
自从我看上他老婆 Carlson就不听我话了
Carlson won't listen to/me since I hit on his wife.
你还知道!
You knew!
天哪 我以为我看上的是他女儿
God no,I thought I was/hitting on his daughter.
你是委员会的 他会听你的
Look,you're on the/committee.He'll listen to you.
我是"辣妹委员会"消息栏的热情读者
I'm an avid reader of "committees/with hotties" message boards.
阿莫西林 500毫克 静脉注射
Amoxicillin,500 milligrams I.V.
大医院的研究表明 快乐的病人恢复更快
Studies conducted in major hospitals/indicate that happy patients recover faster.
我公寓的研究表明 电视让人快乐
Studies conducted in my apartment/show that tv makes people happy.
付费频道效果特别显著
Premium channels have a/particularly striking effect.
向病人收取有线电视费每月可增加1.3万收入
Charging patients for cable is/bringing in 13 grand a month.
除非这不公正待遇被纠正/不然我每天浪费1.3万
Until this injustice is righted,I/am going to waste 13 grand a day.
扔掉$2.49了
It's $2.49 down.
做个心电图 还有心肌酶检查
Get an ekg and a cardiac enzyme.
如果检查没问题 安排他出院/让他买个吹雪机
If those check out,discharge him/and tell him to get  a snow blower.
1.3万除以4美分是多少?
How much is 13 grand divided by $.04?
我不会给你有线电视的
I am not giving you cable.
你就靠公共频道生存下去吧
You're gonna have to somehow survive/with the broadcast networks alone.
星期二这样我没问题/(House每周二播出)
I'll be fine on tuesdays.
如果探伤仪的声波能震碎鸡蛋
If sound waves  from the/flaw detector  break the egg,
就能安全粉碎你的肾结石
it should safely dissolve/your kidney stone.
这行不通的
This isn't going to work.
没理由行不通啊
there's no reason  it shouldn'T.
声波也是声波
Sound waves are sound waves.
石头都是石头
Stones are stones.
有些石头更大
Some are bigger than others.
还在我体内
Some are inside me.
情况怎么样 百战天龙小队?
How's it going,team macgyver?
哦 不错
Oh,great.
看不了有线电视/却能在高清晰电视上看南极
I can't get cable,but I can/get the south pole on hi-def.
差不多准备开始试验了
We're almost ready to start the test.
试验?
test?
福特公司试验埃塞尔了吗?
Did ford test the edsel?
可乐公司试验新可乐了吗?
Did coke test new coke?
莎士比亚试验他最后一部戏"雪橇狗"了吗?
Did shakespeare test his/final play: Snow dogs?
我猜你就是House医生?
I'm guessing you're doctor House?
我还在想你什么时候会路过呢
I was wondering when you might drop by.
她能看见我?
Could she see me?
是的
Oh,yeah.
以为是Jagger为测试音效露面?/(Mick Jagger: 滚石乐队主唱)
Think jagger shows/up for the sound check?
乐队管理人 离开舞台吧
Okay roadies,off the stage.
去急诊室帮Cameron
Go help Cameron in the E.R.
为什么 你不可能是想帮她忙
Why?No way you're just doing her a favor.
急诊室忙得不可开交
E.R.Is standing room only.
意味着Cameron必定会犯错
Which means Cameron's/bound to make a mistake.
找出碴来 我就能勒索她了
Find it so I can blackmail her.
这不是单单为了争夺有线电视的愚蠢战役
As far as you know,this is way more/than just some silly battle over cable.
就绪
ready.
要不把强度调小一些
You you might wanna/just dial it down a smidge.
这我不干
I am not doing this.
你们的肾结石理论基于我有性生活 但
Your kidney stone theory hinges/on me having sex,but
让我猜猜 你像雪一样纯洁
let me guess.You're as/pure as the driven snow.
除非雪像我一样喜欢在上的体位
Only if the snow likes to be on top.
但我来这儿是做心理学研究的
But I am here doing/psychological research.
和研究对象交换体液不算什么好主意
Generally not a good idea to/swap fluids with your subjects.
没有性生活的人也有可能得鸟粪状结石
Struvite stones are possible in/people who don't have sex.
那些声称自己没有性生活的更可能得
They're certainly possible in/people who claim
我尿路没有感染
I've had no U.T.I.S.
排尿没有疼痛
No pain on urination.
你明白我们中谁是真的医生吧
You do realize that only/one of us is a real doctor.
你也得明白我们中谁控制我的行为
You do realize only one of us/has any control over my actions.
Milton医生 你能做化学7项指标检测吗?
Dr. Milton,are you able to run a chem 7?
可以
Yes.
那能告诉我们肾功能是否衰退
That'll tell us if her/kidney function's declining.
如果下降 他就是对的
If it is,he's right.
鸟粪状结石是最有可能的解释
Struvite stone's most/likely explanation.
如果没有 她是对的
If not,she's right.
抱歉 我知道你有多喜欢抓住机会对峙
Sorry,I know how you like to/avoid avoiding confrontation.
做检测 好证明我是对的/同时静脉注射头孢呋辛酯
While we're waiting for that test to/prove me right,start I.V.Cefuroxime.
防止结石感染在肾扩散
Keep the infection in the stone/from wiping out your kidneys.
做好以后 我会把检测结果发给你们
I'll send the chem 7/results when I'm done.
她是个很棒的精神病医生
She's a great psychiatrist.
一个回合 我就退缩了
One session,I've got shrinkage.
House想让我们监视你 向他汇报
House wants us to spy/on you,report back.
你告诉我这个是因为
And you're telling me this because
我们不想这么做
we don't want to do it.
那还有什么问题
I don't see a problem so far.
如果要我们选择惹House生气/还是让你抓狂
If our choice is between pissing/House off or pissing you off,
我们就别无选择了
that's not much of a choice.
除非我给House有线电视/否则你们要搞得我很惨
So unless I give House cable,you're/gonna make my life miserable.
没错
Yes.
事先告诉我 做的时候你们就不会负疚了
And you're telling me this so you/won't feel as guilty when you do it.
没错
Yes.
迎合House的鬼点子不再是我的工作了
Accommodating House's every/whim is not my job anymore.
但这成了我们的工作
But it is ours.
House总会得到他想要的
House will get what he wants.
也许我们应该自己付钱 就说她让步了
Maybe we should just pay for it/ourselves and tell him she folded.
不行
No.
7项化学指标检测结果/表明你的肾功能衰退了
Your chem 7 results show that/your kidney function is declining.
在我看来就是肾结石
Sounds like a kidney stone to me.
可能是胆结石引起我呕吐 脱水/肾功能衰退
The decreased function could be from dehydration/caused by vomiting due to a gallstone.
你同意由指标检测决定是否是鸟粪状结石
You agreed that the chem 7 would/decide if it was a struvite stone.
我同意了做那个测试
I agreed to do the test.
结果有待于解读
The results are up for interpretation.
等我补充了水分 我会在一小时后重做测试
I'll redo the test in an/hour when I'm rehydrated.
用了头孢呋辛酯后有没有什么改善?
Have you noticed any improvement/since starting the cefuroxime?
没什么变化 疼痛差不多一样
Not really.The pain's about the same.
等结果的同时/我们再用地质仪器试验一次
While you're waiting,we should run/another test with the geology equipment.
你没用头孢呋辛酯
You're not taking the cefuroxime.
她惯用右手
she's right handed.
就是说她会在左胳膊挂静脉点滴
Means she would've put/the I.V.In her left arm.
胳膊里有滴管会让人难以曲肘喝水!
Catheter in the arm makes it hard to bend/the elbow the way people do when they drink!
我们的药物量有限 我不打算浪费
We have a limited supply of medication/and I'm not about to waste it.
上次我核实的是/你们医生的数量也很有限
Last I checked,you had a/limited supply of doctors.
就在我生病前/我的一个同事股动脉被割断了
Right before I got sick,one of my/crew members severed his femoral artery.
他需要头孢呋辛酯
He needs the cefuroxime.
是啊 他有优先权
Right,he called dibs.
他的需要是确定无疑的
His need is definitive.
我的不过是猜测
Mine is speculative.
你呼吸加快了
You're breathing fast.
那是因为我很生气!
It's because I'm pissed off!
抬起你的下巴
Lift up your chin.
让我看你的气管
Show me your windpipe.
啊!
Ah!
我胸口疼
My chest hurts.
偏离到左边了
It's deviating to the left.
说明她的右肺正在塌缩
Means her right lung is collapsing.
Cate 你身边有人吗?
Cate,is anyone there with you?
Sean去吃饭了
Sean went to the mess.
- 你得叫个人/- 来不及了
- You need to call someone /- there's no time.
找个注射器和针头
Get a syringe and a needle.
- 我为什么要做/- 闭嘴 快找
- Why am I doing /- shut up and look.
她会晕过去的 她需要
She could pass out.She needs
她需要给那个肺重新充气
she needs to reinflate that lung
现在拔出针塞
okay,now pull out the plunger.
我要你扎在自己的右侧
I want you to stab/yourself in your right side
在锁骨中线的第二和第三根肋骨之间
between the second and third/rib in the mid-clavicular line.
等我们找到人去你那儿
by the time we get someone else there,
你已经窒息了
you'll have suffocated.
快照做吧
Just do it.
啊!
Ah!
你乖乖听我话不是挺好
See all the good stuff that/happens when you listen to me?
说明不是肾结石
Means it's not a kidney stone.
右侧疼痛 呕吐
Right side pain,vomiting,
现在肺在没有创伤的情况下塌陷
and now a lung that gets/traumatized  without any trauma.
听起来怪怪的 说不定是有古怪
Sounds odd.Probably is odd.
我们应该讨论一下 再打给她
We should discuss/this,then call her back.
别顾虑
Oh,that's fine.
我确信了有经费与南极长途通讯
I made sure we got the/south pole long distance plan.
- 你最新的肾功能报告显示/- 我知道它表明什么 是我做的测试
- Your latest kidney function test shows /- I know what it shows.I ran it.
你打断的次数越多/我的炫耀演讲就要越长时间
The more you interrupt,the longer/my grandstanding is gonna take.
什么时候开始你让病人参加鉴别诊断了?
Since when do you let patients/participate in differentials?
自从病人和医生是同一个人开始
Nce the patient and her doctor/happen to be the same person.
你的肾功能还在衰退
Your kidney function is still declining.
说明你肾脏有问题
Means you havea kidney problem.
但这个问题不需要抗生素
But not one that needed antibiotics.
我们一样 都错了
Makes us equally wrong.
不 我们都错了 但程度不一样
No,makes us both wrong.Not equally.
你多错了六倍
You were at least six wronger.
你离境时做结核菌素检测了吗?
They run a ppd before you shipped out?
我和这里每个人都做了 不是肺结核
On me and everybody/else here.It's not T.B.
打扰一下
Excuse us a second.
癌症解释了症状
cancer explains the symptoms.
肺里或肾脏的肿瘤会把结块丢到其他器官
A tumor in her lung or kidney that/threw a clot to the other organ.
你是在担心肿瘤会偷听
And you're worried the/tumor might overhear,
知道我们发现它了
realize we're on to it.
即使对于不在南极的人/癌症也是让人难以接受的诊断
Cancer's a hard diagnosis for patients/even when they're not in the south pole.
我们应该搞清楚 也许叫Wilson来
We should figure this/out,maybe bring Wilson in.
很明显你们两个觉得我情况不妙
Obviously you two think I'm in bad shape.
除非你觉得肿瘤算糟糕
Only if you count the tumor.
House!
可能在你腹部
Probably in your abdomen.
但你没什么先进的成象仪器
But you don't have  any/advanced imaging equipment.
也没有外科医生能做活检 没有切片染色剂
You also don't have a surgeon to biopsy/it,any stains to use on the slide,
或是肿瘤学家分析它
or an oncologist to analyze it.
要握着她的手安慰 也太远了
Too far away to hold her hand.
我有癌症?
I have cancer?
有可能
Possibly.
既然你唯一的成象仪器是X射线/只能将就了
Since the only imaging equipment/you have is x-ray,let's start there.
X射线透视你整个身体
X-ray your entire body.
等我做好了就上传图像
I'll upload the images when I'm done.
祝好运
Good for you
她很烦人
she's annoying.
不肯吃抗生素 因为其他人会用的着
Refused to take the antibiotics/because other people might need them.
她说她关心其他人?
She said she cares about other people?
真会装模作样
What a poser.
尿路平片无问题
K.U.B. is clean.
你不喜欢她 是因为她是精神病学家
You don't like her because/she's a psychiatrist.
我这人性格复杂
I'm a complicated man.
所以我厌恶她的原因也很复杂
I loathe her for many reasons.
这么需要看精神病医生的人/却这么诋毁精神病医生 真是史无前例
Never before has a profession been so/decried by someone who needed it so badly.
你这是在说变性妓女的坏话呀
You talk a lot of/smack about tranny hookers.
- 纵隔肿大的淋巴结/- 淋巴瘤
- Enlarged mediastinal node./- Lymphoma.
有可能 但不做活检无法确定
Probably,but we can't/confirm it  without a biopsy.
没有染色剂 无法就活检组织进行分析
You can't analyze a/biopsy without a stain.
无法活检
We can't biopsy.
因为他们那没有染色剂
'Cause they don't have stains down there.
我们要找出替代品
We need a substitute.
没有手术小组和手术室/她也没法对淋巴结进行活检
She can't biopsy that node/without a surgical team and an o.R.
只要颜色够深 就能当成染色剂用
Anything with a strong/color could work as a stain.
打印机墨水 食品着色料 咖啡
Printer ink,food coloring,coffee.
不用了 谢谢
No thanks.
找一个接近表层的淋巴结/这样她就能自己活检
We'll find a node closer to/the surface one she can biopsy.
有道理
That makes sense.
有道理?
That makes sense?
我先说的
I said it first.
语气这么平静
In a shockingly calm manner
跟你胡搅蛮缠了半分钟
after I'd just been jerking/you around for 30 seconds
你没抱怨也没分析我胡搅蛮缠的原因
without you complaining or/analyzing said jerking.
因为我很成熟
I was being mature.
穿着浅紫色的衬衫
In a lavender shirt.
看来有什么事情让你心情很好
You for some reason are happy.
你管得着吗?
How dare you?
X光片显示没有其他异常淋巴结
The x-rays don't show any/other abnormal nodes.
初期异常淋巴结X光片照不出来/但能触摸感觉到
Abnormal nodes can be felt before/they can be seen on an x-ray.
这衬衫是特意穿给某人看的
You're wearing that shirt for someone.
穿给卫生部看的/他们不赞同肿瘤科医生光膀子上班
The health department.They/frown on topless oncology.
你打算让她做体检?
You're gonna do a physical?
不得不做
Have to.
你和Foreman就留在这找染色剂
You and foreman are gonna/be here looking for a stain.
我能自检 你没必要看
I can do the physical.There's/no reason to watch.
我至少能想出三大理由
I can think of at least three reasons.
一条还是医学上的
One of them's medical.
你在哪?
Where are you?
不在办公室里
Not in your office.
你不在医院 我也没必要呆在那
You're not in the hospital.No/reason for me to be.
我不会在你公寓里宽衣解带的
I am not undressing for/you in your apartment.
你不在我公寓啊
You're not in my apartment.
隔着大半个地球呢
You're three quarters of a world away.
我保证不会对你放肆的
I promise not to get fresh.
我不会脱的
I'm not taking off my clothes.
我俩总得有个人脱啊
One of us has to.
让我看看你家
Show me your place.
呃 有墙壁地板 还有屋顶
Uh,it's got walls,a floor,and/in some places,a roof.
你不让我看 我也不会让你看的
I am not exposing/myself without some reciprocity.
不过是公寓而已 又不是我的心
It's my apartment.It's not my soul.
客厅
Living room.
慢点
Slow down.
恩 这么多书
Huh,lots of books.
我猜都是医学的
I'm betting all medical.
除非把Jenna Jameson(性感女星)的自传/当做妇科学教材
Only if you count jenna jameson's/autobiography as a gynecological text.
不能让人笑开怀的小说 就不值一看
Fiction is a waste of time/unless you can laugh at it.
我就爱笑开怀
I love to laugh.
继续
Moving on.
回放
Back up.
失眠有多严重?
How bad is the insomnia?
我问具体点
Let me clarify that.
是不是总得喝上两三杯威士忌/才能在电视前晕个不省人事?
Do you drink two or three scotches/before passing out in front of the tv?
你错得远了
You are so far off.
是波旁酒
It's bourbon.
哪都没照片
No photos anywhere.
家人朋友都不重要?
Family and friends aren't important?
你病了
Well,you're sick.
身边有二十号人 也只有一个来看你
You got 20 people down the hall/and you've had exactly one visitor.
我不想他们担心
I don't want tpanic anyone.
你不想和人打交道才对
You don't like people.
- 躲在冰旮旯里 这样别人就/- 别把你的想法映射到我身上
- You hide on that ice cube so people /- stop projecting.
你自己不爱社交/所以就断定我也不爱
You're anti-social,so you/assume I'm anti-social.
我这就脱光光 你也闭嘴 怎样?
How about if I just get/naked and you shut up?
要是我觉得能让你脱光光的话/早就那么做了
If I thought I could get you/naked,I would've led with that.
你宁可让我看你的心/也不会让我看你的腿
You'd rather show me/your soul than your leg.
了不起 把我看透了
Great,you got me all figured out.
现在试着治好我吧?
You gonna trand fix me now?
我从没说过你需要治疗
I never said you needed fixing.
他让她参与会诊
He's letting her take/part in the differentials.
当然了
Of course he is.
他喜欢她
He likes her.
重大新闻/意大利面酱不能当作淋巴组织染色剂
Big shock,spaghetti sauce doesn't/work as a lymph tissue stain.
我来试试咖啡
I'll try the coffee.
House烦她 也不当她是医生尊重她
He's annoyed by her,doesn't/respect heras a doctor,
经常性侮辱她
constantly insults her.
House献殷勤的方式嘛
That's House's version of courtship.
噢 天啊 那他不是追求我好多年了
Oh,god.He's been wooing me for years.
她是他的绝配
She's the perfect woman for him.
为了工作愿意奔赴天涯海角
Willing to literally go to the/end of the earth for her career,
没法真正谈恋爱
making her unavailable for/a real relationship.
更妙的是还身患神秘疾病
And she's afflicted with/a mysterious illness.
酱油不行
Soy sauce is a no-go.
我们得在这耗一整夜了
We're gonna be here all night.
你脱个衣服要多久啊?
How long does it take you to get naked?
这可是南极
It's the south pole.
我穿了好多
I wear a lot of layers.
好了
Okay,ready.
啊!
Bah!
我看见袜子了!
I saw socks.
这可不算脱光光
That's not naked.
我没提过这里是冰天雪地吗?
Have I mentioned it's freezing here?
等到脚上也开始长淋巴结
When they discover lymph nodes in feet,
我会脱袜子的
I will take off my socks.
用右手触诊淋巴结
Use your right hand to palpate the nodes.
能摸到的就能做活检
Any node you can feel/is one you can biopsy.
从胸部开始
Let's start with your breasts,
摸到臀 然后
move down to the ass,then
我本想从脖子开始向下的
I was thinking go from the/neck and work my way down.
恩 那也行
Well you could,
要是在摸到胸部前 就有所发现/我就要遗憾终身了
but I'd never forgive myself if we found/something before we got to your breasts.
从颈前淋巴结开始
I'm starting with the/anterior cervical nodes.
侧转头部
Turn your head.
找准胸锁乳突肌
Locate the scm muscle.
我知道怎么找淋巴结
I know how to find my lymph nodes.
是在关爱内在自我这课之前学的/还是之后学的?
They teach you that before or after the/class on fondling your inner child?
无肿大 无触痛
No swelling,no tenderness,
我能听到 House
and I can hear that,House.
不过是想帮你放松
Just thought it might help you relax.
腋下淋巴结呢?
anything in the axillary nodes?
没问题
All clear.
两边都没有
Both sides.
将手轻放到胸骨上/寻找淋巴结
Slide your hand to your/sternum,probe for nodes.
慢慢下移
Moving slowly downward.
移到哪 House?
Down to what,House?
抱歉 听不清 你呼吸太重了
Sorry,can't hear you on/account of your heavy breathing.
我得吸氧才行的 智障
I'm supposed to be on oxygen,you tool.
停住
Hold it.
手指本应陷的更深
Your fingers didn't go quite as deep.
再按一下那个淋巴结
Feel that node again.
肿了
it it's swollen.
看来你马上就可以做活检了
Looks like you're doing a biopsy.
基本无感觉了
it's pretty numb.
好的 深呼吸
okay,take a deep breath
将针刺入淋巴结
and insert the needle in the node.
加油 Cate
Come on,cate.
一鼓作气完成活检
Let's get this over with.
你叫的是她的名字
You used her name.
为了顺利开展工作而已 Bob
Just trying to move things along,bob.
行 我刺进去了
Okay,I'm in.
往回抽注射器
You need to pull back on the syringe.
再用力
You need to pull harder.
啊!
Ah!
你没事吧?
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
"你没事吧?"
"Are you okay?"
一个很正常的医学问题
It's a valid medical question.
我以前从没听过你问病人这个问题
I have never heard you ask/a patient that question.
你从没问过我这个问题
You've never asked me that question,
我喝醉酒从楼梯上摔下来的时候/你都没问过
and you've seen me fall/down a flight of stairs drunk.
你跟她上过床了
You've slept with her.
我俩中间隔着十万八千里呢
She's 9,000 miles away.
当我身体某个部分展开的时候
And while a certain/part of me unfurled
打住 你
no,you
总之你和她很亲密
somehow you've been intimate with her.
你干嘛跟着我?
Why are e you following me?
不是你跟着我吗?
Thought you were following me.
不 肯定是你在跟着我
No,you are definitely following me.
- 你去哪?/- 出去吃午饭
- Where are you going?/- Out to lunch.
你从不出去吃午饭
You never go outto lunch.
说明你出去吃饭是有原因的
Means there's a reason you're/going out to lunch.
我看是因为某人
I assume that reason is a human being.
或是三明治
Or a sandwich.
这里有三明治卖
Sandwiches can come here.
这里也有人啊
So can human beings.
可她不在这 所以我觉得很有趣
Yet she's not,which I find interesting.
我走了
I'm leaving now.
真巧啊 同路
Small world.
你打算跟着上我的车吗?
Are you going to follow me into my car?
反正有两个车门
It's got two doors.
听着  我之所以没告诉你 是因为
Okay,look  the reason/I haven't told you is
撤回你的手下 House
call off your dogs,House.
他们审问我的病人
Your little helpers are/interrogating my patients,
偷走图表 拦截处方
swiping my charts,intercepting/prescriptions.
为什么你觉得是我
Why would you think that I'm
我又不是白痴
because I'm not a moron.
肯定是你在幕后操纵
You had to be pulling the strings here.
你以为让我过得苦不堪言/我就会同意你装有线电视?
You think that because they make me/miserable I'm gonna give you cable?
假定你说的是对的
Let's assume that's true.
听着也确实挺像的/你打算怎么办?
And it certainly sounds like it/might be.What are you gonna do?
什么也不做
Nothing.
我向预算委员会辞职了
I resigned from the budget committee.
我加入委员会是想帮助医院
I only joined the/committee to help the hospital.
你让我成了累赘
You made me a liability.
现在我无权干预医院的有线电视政策了
I now have zero influence over/the hospital's cable policy.
干得漂亮
Well done.
行不通
It didn't work.
- 没有更/- 把这些贴起来
- There's nothing more that /- put these up.
"免费罗特韦尔犬大赠送
"Free rottweiler puppies.
请于晚11点至早5点间 拨打如下号码"
Please call after 11:00/pm and before 5:00 am."
这不是Cameron家的电话吗?
Is this Cameron's home number?
我想再要只小狗
I love a new puppy.
之前那只味道好极了
That last one was delicious.
- 鲜嫩可口/- 没必要折磨她
- Very t/- there's no point in torturing her.
她能辞职的话 也就能复职
If she can resign,she can unresign.
去玩玩核战危机(一款游戏)
Go to defcon one.
这次不要干等她犯错/想办法让她出错
Forget waiting for a/mistake,make her make one.
你希望我们去陷害一名医生
You want us to sabotage another doctor,
可能还会危害到病人/就是为了让你能看有线电视?
possibly harm a patient,all/so you can have cable.
别给病人留下永久性伤害就行
Harm suggests permanent damage.
让她犯错 然后你们纠正错误
Get her to screw up,then fix it.
噢 这次办事前/不准事先和她打招呼
Oh,and this time don't tell her what/you're gonna do before you do it.
那么 淋巴结该在红酒里泡多久?
So,um,how long do I let the lymph/node marinate in the red wine?
现在应该好了
It should be ready now.
试着调高摄像头的放大倍率
Try increasing the/magnification on the camera.
我给几个医院的同事发邮件/了解了一下你的情况
You know,I e-mailed a couple/colleagues at the hospital about you.
你调查我 而不是House?
You're checking up on me,not House?
是啊 House是个直来直往的人/聪明的混蛋
Yeah,well House is/straightforward,brilliant,and an ass.
三分之二都是优点/明显占了一大半
Two out of three good/qualities,clear majority.
而你呢 恰好相反 完美无缺
Where as you,on the other/hand,have a perfect score.
有责任感 心地善良 有人情味
You are responsible,nice,human.
而你却是House最好的朋友
And yet you're House's best friend.
打住
Hold there.
这让你觉得他私底下比看起来更好?
Makes you think he's/secretly nicer than he seems?
让我觉得你私底下没有看起来那么好
Makes me think that you're secretly/a lot less nice than you seem.
你经常侮辱你的医生吗?
Do you always insult your doctors?
不是侮辱
It's not an insult.
总是老好人就成滥好人了
Indiscriminate niceness is overrated.
难怪他喜欢你
No wonder he likes you.
从这张载玻片来看 你没得癌症
Based on this slide,you/do not have cancer.
噢 谢天谢地
Oh.Thank god.
确实有些发炎 表明可能
I do see some/inflammation which could mean
- 啊/- Cate?
- ah mm /- cate?
你还好吧?
You all right?
我左侧 很痛
My left side hurts.Um
和右侧疼痛一模一样
it's the same pain that/I had on the right.
另一个肾脏
Your other kidney.
不 我希望是 可能是!
No,I hope it's/something,um it's maybe  ah!
噢 不!
Oh,no!
我不行了
I'm screwed.
坏消息是你两个肾都不行了
bad news is you're 0 for/2 in the kidney department.
有好消息吗?
Is there good news?
你回家了
You're back at home.
当然有
Of course.
家里有有线电视
There's cable.
还能不穿裤子做事
And the freedom to work pant-free.
确实是好消息
That is good news.
Wilson发现你的活检组织有发炎迹象
Wilson found signs of/inflammation in your biopsy.
炎症加上肾衰竭表明是自身免疫性疾病
That plus the two failing kidneys/points to autoimmune disease.
可能是全身性红斑狼疮或血管炎
Probably sle or vasculitis.
两者都可用强的松进行治疗
Treatment for both is prednisone.
注射100毫克
Start with 100 milligrams
自身免疫性疾病不过是你的最新推断而已
autoimmune is just your latest theory.
就像之前的癌症 还有肾结石
Like cancer before that,and/a kidney stone before.
接受强的松治疗 如果有所好转 你就可以确诊了
Take the prednisone,you'll get/better,that'll be your confirmation.
你用药就像火灾物品大拍卖似的
You practice medicine like/it's a fire sale.
白白浪费了那些抗生素和X光检测...
You've wasted antibiotics,x-rays
那不算浪费 我们排除了...
that was not a waste.We ruled out
我们的一个队员患有哮喘
we have a crew member/here who has asthma.
如果我把强的松都用完了/他一旦发作便会死的
If he has an episode after I've/used up the prednisone,he'll die.
反正他迟早都得死
There's a good chance he's/gonna die anyway,
因为你死了 就没有医生帮他
since there won't be a/doctor there to help him.
拿出自体免疫病的证据
Show me proof that it's autoimmune
那我就服用强的松
and then I'll take the prednisone.
我们应该让她离开那里
we should send her outside.
是啊 让她一直朝北走 直到看见医院为止
Right,just tell her to head north/until she runs into a hospital.
自体免疫病就是炎症极度失调
Autoimmune diseasesare basically/inflammation running wild.
可以使用冷冻法治疗/比如在扭伤的足踝上敷冰块
Extreme cold has been used as treatment,like/putting ice on a sprained ankle.
如果她在室外能感觉好转 那就是自体免疫病
She starts to feel better outside,we/know it's autoimmune.
那是我的钱包吗?
Is that my wallet?
是的 你可以拿回去了
Yeah,you can have it back.
我已经翻过了
I've already been through it.
在足踝上敷冰块可真是个好比喻
I like your "ice on a sprain" metaphor.
显得我们不是在谋杀她
Makes it seem like we're not killing her.
她只要在室外待上五分钟就好了
She'd only need to be/outside five minutes.
连手套也不戴
Without her mittens.
妈妈说这样不好哦
Mom told me that was a bad idea.
那里气温还不到零下70度 (摄氏-56度)/而她两个肾脏都在衰竭
Especially that winter it was 70/below and I had dual kidney failure.
这主意很好 你该觉得完美...
This is a good idea.It's/perfect for you
实验性 高风险
experimental,risky.
Wilson说得对 你关心...
Wilson's right.You care about
你没拿现金 但拿走了收据?
you didn't touch the/cash,but you took the receipts?
190美元的餐厅帐单
$190 restaurant tab.
应该有甜品 可能还喝了酒
That's dessert,probably booze.
看来这段饭吃得时间够长
Means you lingered.
至少是第三次约会了
Means it's at least the third date.
- 说明.../- 你要去哪?
- Means /- where are you going?
去找拿了我工资 该提出医学见解的人
To talk to the people I pay/to come up with medical ideas.
没什么好办法了
There are no ideas.
自体免疫病需要检测抗核抗体
The test for autoimmune is A.N.A.
除非企鹅拉出台自体免疫分析仪/她无法...
Unless penguins poop immuno/analyzers,she's not
在抗核抗体检测出现之前/如果有人得了自体免疫病
before A.N.A.Testing,people/had autoimmune diseases.
是怎么诊断的?
How did they know?
C3补体
C3.
- 再之前呢/- 红斑性狼疮血液测试
- Before that./- L.E.Prep.
但是她没有可控孔度玻璃珠
But she doesn't have  any/controlled pore glass beads.
用不着那个
You don't need them.
当你晃动试管的时候/回形针会毁坏部分血液细胞
When you shake the test tube,the paper clip/will damage some of your blood cells.
如果你有自体免疫病
If you have an autoimmune disease,
免疫系统会吞噬受损细胞
your immune system will gorge/itself  on the damaged cells.
它们会肿大 显微镜下可以观察到
They'll get big and fat so you/can see 'em under a microscope.
感觉怎么样?
How you doing?
没变化
No change.
在细胞变大之前 我应该等多久?
So how long should I give the cells/to fatten up before I check them?
几个小时
Couple hours.
你也可以不做伪君子/现在就开始服用强的松
Or you could stop being a hypocrite/and take the prednisone now.
不服从你的意志就是伪君子?
Not bending to your/will makes me a hypocrite?
如果你的精神病人也需要检测结果
If your psych/patients demanded lab results,
你将无法做出诊断
you'd never make a diagnosis.
那么说我错了
So I'm wrong.
你每夜甜蜜入睡/生活也如你梦想的一般美好
You sleep like a baby,your life/is unfolding as you dreamed.
每个人都是可悲的
Everyone is miserable.
这无法改变 因为人们不会改变
You don't change that because/people don't change.
你希望这么想/这样就不用为自己的可悲负责
You want to believe that because then you're/freed from any responsibility  for your misery.
哦 打住吧
Oh,shut up.
我已经听Wilson说够了
I get enough of this from Wilson.
可你照样还和他在一起
And yet you keep hanging out with him.
而且据我所知
And from what I hear,
你跟我相处的时间/比其他任何病人都要长
you have spent more time with/me than with any other patient.
那抱歉了
Sorry about that.
有结果就告诉我
Call me when you get the results.
病人如何了?
How's your patient?
她得的是自体免疫病
She has an autoimmune disease.
告诉精神科  她硬是不承认
Tell the psych/department she's in denial.
我必须解雇Cameron
I had to fire Cameron.
什么?
What?
怎么回事?
What happened?
65岁男子因髋骨骨折被送进急诊室
65-year-old man came into/the E.R.With a hip fracture.
Cameron给他注射了杜冷丁
Cameron gave him demerol.
可病人在服用单胺氧化酶抑制剂
The guy was on an M.A.O.I.
因此出现了高血压危象
Put him into a hypertensive crisis.
没事了吗?
Is he gonna live?
幸好Taub及时发现了
Taub caught the error in time.
如果她愿意承认错误/我还能安排她暂时停职
If she'd just admitted the mistake,maybe/I could've just suspended her.
可她已经在收拾了 你要打个招呼吗
But she's packing up,if/you want to say good-bye.
再过几分钟 南极就会打电话来了
We should be hearing from the/south pole in a few minutes.
没别的了?
That's it?
爱莫能助
There's nothing to be done.
她搞砸了
She screwed up.
除了自己 她怨不得别人
She's got no one to blame but herself.
我得去和Cameron谈谈
I gotta go talk to Cameron.
Cuddy不会因为一个错误就把她怎么样的
Cuddy wouldn't can her for one screw-up.
她要是不留情 就不会来找我
And if she did,she wouldn't come to me.
她要是真怎么着/也不会开口就问"病人如何了"
And if she did,she wouldn't/open with,"how's your patient."
- 她要是.../- 她为什么要撒谎?
- And if she did /- why would she lie?
古老的问题啊
Timeless question.
这一次 她是和你的同事合谋
In this case,she conspired with/your coworkers to teach me
想教育我 有些东西比有线电视更重要
that some things are/more important than cable.
而我将教育他们 他们错了
And I'm gonna have to teach/them that they're wrong.
快点 南极应该打电话来了
Come on,south pole really/should be calling.
红斑性狼疮血液测试是阴性
L.E.Prep test was negative.
不是自体免疫病
It's not autoimmune.
就基于一个回形针测试的结果?
You're basing that on a/test done wh a paperclip.
用强的松就是了
Just take the prednisone.
给我别的诊断假设 或者找别的测试方法
Either find another diagnosis/or find another test.
还有个方法
There is one way.
有一种试验药物 叫做...
You can take this/experimental drug called
强的松!
prednisone!
- 当你的肾脏恢复功能.../- 还有一种测试
- Your kidneys start working /- there is another test.
Foreman刚才可能信号不大好
Oh,I I think foreman may've/just broken up there.
他要说的是"没有其他测试了"
What he actually said was/"there is no other test."
如果你有自体免疫病
if you have an autoimmune disease,
肾脏的疼痛在低温下就会缓解
exposure to the cold should/decrease your kidney pain.
我去室外 会有答案?
If I go outside,we'll have our answer?
而你也知道这个?
And you knew about this?
但是我拒绝了/因为冻僵了就很难把针管插进胳膊
I rejected it because if you're frozen solid,it's/hard to get the needles into your arms.
我得在外面待上多久?
How long do I need to stay out?
至少五分钟
At least five minutes.
一个健康的人在室外八分钟就会冻死
Eight minutes outside would/kill a healthy person.
健康的人可不需要氧气面罩
And healthy people don't/suck on oxygen masks.
健康的人可以小便
Healthy people can pee.
我去找Sean 让他和我一起
I'll go get sean,have him come with me.
你服用强的松就得了!
Just take the prednisone.
等我回来再用
Once I come inside.
如果是自体免疫病的话
If it's autoimmune.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
我想她没事
Oh,I'm sure she's just fine.
Cate?
去查查那里谁有手机
See if there's anyone down/there who has a cell phone.
用了20分钟才接上那里的工程师
took the station mechanic20/minutes to respond.
她已经进入昏迷状态了
She'd already slipped into a coma.
注射了强的松 但是没有好转
Started her on/prednisone,but no improvement.
说明不是自体免疫病
Means it's not autoimmune.
幸好她昏迷了 否则又要自鸣得意
Good thing she's in a coma,or/we'd have to listen to her gloat.
我们要去哪?
And where are we going?
去找我手下那些有用的人
To find the useful members of my team.
你决定放他一马了?
You're letting him off the hook?
满意了?
Happy?
你害我看不到韩语版的"法律与秩序"了
Because of you,I'm not gonna be able/to watch law and order in korean.
我在这干吗?
Why am I here?
因为我想问问你女朋友的事情
Because I want to ask/you about your girlfriend.
肯定是我认识的人/否则你就告诉我名字了
I must know who she is or/you'd have told me her name.
她没有名字的 这是先天缺陷
She doesn't have a name.It's/some sort of birth defect.
我们俩都认识的人大概只有12个
There's only about 12/people we both know.
其中5个我不记得名字了 所以只剩下...
I can't remember five of/their names,so we're down to
Cuddy 还有你的前妻...
cuddy,your ex-wives
你妈妈
your mama
你得做一个肾功能检测
you need to run a kidney function test.
是啊 如果她没有昏迷的话
Yes,if only she wasn't in a coma
我们可以让她来做个测试/找出致使她昏迷的原因
we could get her to run a test/to find out why she's in a coma.
结果很可能是自相矛盾的
The results would likely be paradoxical.
不可能是Cuddy 因为你不是同志
Can't be cuddy,'cause you're straight.
- 不可能是.../- 可以教那个工程师来做检测
- Can't be /- we could talk the mechanic through the test.
太复杂了
Too complicated.
除非他口渴了
Unless he's thirsty.
喝她的尿液?
Drink her urine?
如果味道很浓很重 说明是肾脏的问题
If it has a strong,concentrated taste,it/means the problem's in her kidneys.
味道很淡则说明是大脑问题
Watery taste means it's her brain.
这样你就能治好她了?
And then you can fix it?
就算是吧
Let's say yeah.
我怎么取出她的尿液?
How do I get the urine out of her?
找一根导尿管 然后插入...
Take a straight catheter and insert it
你就只有这个问题?
these are your only questions?
不是 "安不安全?"
Not,"is it safe?"
或者 "有没有别的方法?"
Or,"is there another way?"
或者 "你发神经了吗?"
Or,"are you out of your minds?"
- 既然你让我这么做.../- 慢着
- You wouldn't ask me if /- wait a second.
你爱她
You're in love with her.
所以你巴不得她脱光了 还要喝一杯
That explains why you're so eager/to get her naked,then have a drink.
而大多数男人喜欢先喝再脱
'Cause most guys like to/go the other way around.
我爱不爱她与你何干?
Why do you care how I feel about her?
因为现在我知道 你会不惜一切来救她
Because now I know that I can get/you to do anything to save her.
告诉他怎么弄到喝的
Tell him how to tap the keg.
你们害Cameron被炒了
You got Cameron fired.
本来Cuddy是不应该发现的
Uh,cuddy wasn't supposed to find out.
可不是嘛!
No kidding!
帮我搞来有线电视有多困难啊?
Get me cable.How tough can that be?
害得一个女人丢了工作
Cost a woman her job.
你们只有说对一句话 才能避免被炒鱿鱼
There's only one thing you can/say to keep me from firing you.
Cameron没被解雇
Cameron wasn't fired.
错了
Wrong.
- 你知道了?/- 我们被炒了吗?
- You know?/- We're still fired?
那句话是提示你们说出正确的台词
That should be a hint as to/what you're supposed to say.
- 对不起/- 错了
- We're sorry./- Wrong.
我爱你
I love you.
错了
Wrong.
这是场游戏吗?
this is a game?
先是去陷害同事/现在还得要揣摩你的心思?
First we have to screw with our coworker  and now we/have to try to figure out  what you want us to say?
简直荒谬 我不玩了
This is insane.I'm not playing.
正确
Right.
两天前你们就该这么说了
Should've said this two days ago.
别想和我玩游戏
Do not play games with me.
一来你们会输 你们还不够格
Number one,you're going to/lose.You're just not ready.
二来 游戏目的就是让你们停止游戏
Number two,the game was to/force you to stop playing games.
我需要你们挺直腰板
I need you to stand up to me.
...来面对我/不要整日担心是否会丢饭碗
Challenge me.I need you to stop/worrying  about getting fired.
快去帮我付有线电视费
Go pay for my cable.
不!
No!
我不是指反对这个!
I didn't mean on this.
严肃点 我需要有线电视
Seriously,I need cable.
牛奶 牛奶 柠檬汁
Milk,milk,lemonade.
味道淡得像水
Uh,this tastes kind of watery.
坏消息
That's bad news.
要么是颅内压升高
Either increased intracranial pressure or
要么就是下丘脑出了问题
something's wrong with her hypothalamus.
你们如何诊断是哪一种?
How do you figure out which one it is?
我们什么都不做
We don't do anything.
你得在她颅骨上钻一个洞
You're gonna drill a hole in her skull.
若她恢复意识 那就是颅内压升高
If she regains consciousness,it's/increased intracranial pressure.
如果是另一种病因呢?
And if it's the other thing?
她会死
She'll die.
如果是下丘脑的问题 反正她也死定了
But if it's the/hypothalamus,she's dead anyway.
如果问题在于颅内压/我照你说的做 她就会好吗?
If the problem is the pressure in her/brain,and I fix it,is she gonna be all better?
不 但会为我们争取到更多的诊断时间
Nope,but it'll give us more/time to figure out what's wrong.
我得去找别人 我做不了这个
I have to get someone/else.I can't do this.
你爱她
You love her
对吗?
right?
你愿意不惜一切来救她
You'd do anything to save her.
不是这样
Not this.
我做不了这个
I can't do this.
如果我做了什么而害死她
If if she dies because of/something that I did,then I
听着 听着
listen,listen.
我不会让你伤害她的
I am not going to let you hurt her.
明白吗?
Okay?
可是现在....
Now please .
这是她唯一的机会
this is her only chance.
好的
Okay.
哇 挺容易嘛
Well,that was easy.
好了 她的头部已经固定
okay,her head is stabilized
钻头也消过毒了
and the drill bit is sterile.
把钻头靠在她前额的左上部
Place the drill bit against  the/upper left part of her forehead.
太阳穴上一英寸
About an inch above the temple.
钻不动了
It's not going anywhere.
骨头比木头硬 一直钻下去
Bone's harder than wood.Lean into it.
颅骨厚度只有1/4英寸
The skull's only a quarter-inch thick.
钻到一半的时候 用短脉冲
Once you're midway/through,drill in shorter bursts.
如果钻头从她大脑另一边出来 那你就过度了
If it comes out the other/side,you've gone too far.
好了 现在怎么办 怎么办?
Okay,now what?Now what?
让血液流出来
Let the fluid drain.
她醒过来了 醒过来了
She's waking up.She's waking up.
Sean?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
南极的医生脱离昏迷状态了
south pole doc is out of her coma,
现在有了新的症状 颅内压升高
and now we have a new symptom:/Increased intracranial pressure.
我们上外边来干吗?
why are we out here?
里面是病人的房间
that's the patient room.
颅内压 肾脏问题 还有肺衰竭 等于什么?
Icp plus kidney problems/plus lung collapse equals?
最大的可能性是 肿瘤正在产生血块
The most likely suspect is/a tumor throwing off clots.
我们已经排除了癌症
We ruled out cancer.
没排除血块
But not clots.
什么会导致血块?
What causes blood clots?
细菌性心内膜炎
Bacterial endocarditis.
但是她没有发烧
Not without a fever.
深部静脉栓塞 加上卵圆孔未闭合
Deep vein thrombosis/plus an existing pfo.
如果有卵圆孔未闭合/去南极前的体检中会被发现
Pfo would've been discovered in/her pre-south pole physical exam.
如果那些根本不是血块呢?
What if the clots aren't clots?
动脉硬化
Atherosclerosis.
脂肪斑在动脉血管壁上堆积
Fatty plaque builds/upon the arterial walls,
斑块落下 阻碍血液流动
pieces break off,block blood flow.
病情都能解释得了
Explains everything.
致病危险因素 她全都不具备
She has zero risk factors.
别想脂肪了 还是想想血块吧
Forget fat,think clots.
不
No.
你正面反抗我?
You're standing up to me?
是又怎样
Maybe.
说得再清楚些
Just to clarify.
只有你在理时 才能反对我的意见
You should do that when you're right.
抱歉没说清楚
Sorry for the confusion.
- 血块怎么会/- 可能是脂肪的另一形态 比如脂肪栓塞
- how could a clot /- could be a different kind of fat,fat emboli.
确实完全符合
that's a perfect fit
除了这根本不可能!
except it's completely impossible!
骨折未修复才可能导致脂肪栓塞
Fat emboli requires an/unrepaired bone break.
经过X射线透视和体检 我看过她全身
Between the x-ray and the/exam,I've seen her entire
瞧 这正是我需要的勇气
see,that's what I'm talking about.
脱下袜子
Take off her socks.
我自己能行
I could I could do it.
不 我来
No,I got it.
你脚趾骨折了
Your toe is broken.
天哪
Oh,my god.
骨髓流入你的血液
bits of bone marrow have been/leaking in your blood stream.
脂肪栓塞导致肾脏 肺和脑部的血液阻塞
Those fat emboli have caused blockages/in your kidney,lungs,and brain.
可根本不疼
It doesn't even hurt.
寒冷让感觉麻木了
Cold numbs everything.
在手足末端更是如此
Does a particularly great/job on the extremities.
得让趾骨完全折断 好让骨髓不再泄漏
You'll need to close the break/so stop the marrow from leaking.
这回你会觉得疼的
This one you will feel.
你能帮我么?
Will you do it?
他先是喝了你的尿/然后在你颅骨上钻洞
He drilled a hole in your/skull after drinking your pee.
这对他算小意思了
I think he's up for this.
右手抓住她的脚趾
Grab the tip of her/toe with your right hand.
左手捏紧断裂处
hold the break with your other.
数到三 用力拔
On the count of three,pull hard.
一
One
二
two
三
three.
*回到最初*/歌曲: Human  演唱: Civil Twilight
Back to the beginning
用夹板固定脚趾头
now splint your toe.
会好起来
You'll be fine.
*重新找到回家的路*
There's one way back to home again
谢谢你 House
thank you,House.
不用谢我
don't thank me.
是他救了你
He's the one who saved your life.
*我的感受*
What is this I feel?
*为何如此真实*
Why is it so real?
*我该说什么*
What am I to say?
*这只是爱*
It's only love
*只是痛*
it's only pain
*这感觉流经我全身*
it's only feeling That/runs through my veins
他喜欢她
he likes her
一瓶波尔多酒和苏打水
a bottle of the bordeaux/and some sparkling water.
你没有去接她
Well,you didn't pick her up.
说明她也是下了班过来
Which means she's coming from work too.
- 说明你很乐意见她/- 该死
Which means you're comfortable/enough to meet her.Damn.
我以为沿着雪地里自己的脚印往回走/已经把你甩掉了
Thought I lost you when I walked backwards/through my own footprints in the snow.
我可以把人选缩小到3个了
I think I've got it narrowed/down  to three possibilities.
你最好快走 等看见她了/就不算是你猜出来的
Better leave.If you see/her,it'll be cheating.
不是你的前妻
It's not one of your ex-wives.
她们恨我
Because they hate me.
她们不恨他
They don't.
确实该恨你 可是偏偏不
They should,but they don't.
我给她们打过电话了
I called them.
是新人 但我认识
Someone new,but someone I know.
你难道一点不为我高兴么?
Did you ever consider being happy for me?
有一丝丝
Briefly.
她还没来 你就点了葡萄酒
You ordering the/wine before she got here.
女生值得珍惜 House
Girls are good,House.
你也清楚
And you know it.
你喜欢那个姑娘 才能解决了病例
You solved your case because/you cared about that girl.
你要硬撑起男人的气势
You're demonstrating the/illusion of manly confidence.
说明你还没有得到手
Which means you haven't/closed the deal yet.
我到手了
I closed the deal.
我只是喜欢她
I just like her.
还喜欢?
Still?
你知道病人讨厌脚冰凉
You knew your patient hated/having cold feet
因为在体检的时候
because you did a physical exam,
因为你喜欢她
because you liked her
你的理论是 因为我关心她/所以让她穿着袜子?
your theory is I cared,therefore/I let her keep her socks on?
如果这就是爱 我可不想掺和
If that's what love is,then I don't/want to have anything to do with it.
开始是让脚暖和 然后会发生别的
It starts with warm feet,but/leads to other things.
等你长大了 你妈妈和我会向你解释的
Your mom and I will/explain when you're older.
如果我早点让她脱掉袜子
If I'd made her take/them off like I should've,
几天前就该看到脚趾 从而解开病因了
I would've seen the toe and I/would've solved the case days ago.
但你不喜欢她
But you don't care about her.
当然不
of course not.
House不在乎任何人
House doesn't care about anyone.
嗨
Hi.
对不起 我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
蛇蝎女?
Cutthroat bitch?
我叫她 Amber
I call her amber.
她在你怀疑对象名单上么?
Was she on your list?